<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Madhuka MJ</title><link>https://esriee.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Madhuka MJ</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 22:28:03 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://esriee.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Linux I/0 Redirections</title><link>https://esriee.github.io/posts/dataflow/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 22:28:03 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://esriee.github.io/posts/dataflow/</guid><description>When it comes to managing input and output in Linux the kernels handling of I/O redirection is an essential feature that powers many of the system&amp;rsquo;s functionalities.
What is I/O Redirection? I/O redirection in Linux is a mechanism that allows you to change the destination of input and output for commands. by default, linux commands read from the standard input (stdin) and write to the standard output (stdout) and standard error (stderr).</description></item><item><title>BSPWM</title><link>https://esriee.github.io/posts/install-bspwm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:04:24 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://esriee.github.io/posts/install-bspwm/</guid><description>bspwm What is BSPWM? BSPWM is a tiling window manager that arranges windows in a non-overlapping pattern. It is very easy to configure. bspwm doesn&amp;rsquo;t handle any keyboard or pointer inputs a third party program (e.g. sxhkd) is needed in order to translate keyboard and pointer events to bspc invocations.
Follow these step-by-step instructions to install BSPWM on your Linux system:
Install Bspwm Start by installing BSPWM using your package manager.</description></item><item><title>Library</title><link>https://esriee.github.io/library/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://esriee.github.io/library/</guid><description>The Linux Kernel documentation Linux Kernel Documentation
Linux-Insides Excellent blog about linux kernel insides and Boot Process
XV6 MIT Operating System Engineering xv6 OS Introduction Rev.11
PC Assembly Language, Paul A. Carte How Computers Really Work At Lower Level Than In Programming Languages
A Guide To Kernel Exploitation Attacking The Core By Enrico Perla &amp;amp; Massimiliano Oldani Kernel Exploitation Techniques And Mitigation Strategies
Linux Kernel Internals Awesome Book About Linux Kernel 2.</description></item></channel></rss>